Michaela Vojtová

Junior Web Developer

Portugal / EU remote



misacastella@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/michaelavojtova





https://github.com/misavojtova/resume-2021

Summary

I'm a Junior Web Developer constantly improving my technical skills and logical thinking. Currently I'm enrolled in Web Development course at Wild Code School in Lisbon with a main focus of building projects in teams using latest technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React.js, Express, Node.js and MySQL Database. I worked in diverse environments in different countries improving my skills on high level communication, customer satisfaction, problem solving and team work. In my spare time I practice singing; I'm passionate about music and that drove me to get an associate degree at Prague Conservatory.

Experience



React Developer - IDUN Technologies

Dec 2021 - Present - (2 months)

- * Working on a Project for IDUN technologies is an opportunity provided by Wild Code School.
- I'm taking part in creating an internal application in React.js.
- As a team we work on back-end in Node.js, Express.js.
- We are applying scrum methodology. Sprints and user stories.

Technical Support Advisor - Teleperformance

Aug 2020 - Dec 2020 (5 months)

- Trained in MacOS operating system and related products.
- Troubleshooting system and network problems.
- Diagnosing hardware or software faults.
- · Set up new user's accounts
- · Helping customers with password issues.

Coffee Bar Attendant - Nostress Bakery

Sep 2018 - Feb 2019 (6 months)

- Assist customers with product selection.
- · Make recommendations and suggestions based on customer needs.
- Prepare coffee and other beverages.
- · Processing cash transactions.

Education



Wild Code School - Web and mobile development training Sep 2021 - Feb 2022

Web Development at Wild Code School is an intensive five months course that focus on learning HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Git Bash and GitHub. The purpose of this course is to practice those skills on group projects. As a final task we build a project for a company.



🤛 Prague Conservatory - Associate's degree, Singer Jun 2013 – Jun 2019

I dedicated six years of studying popular music and singing at Prague Conservatory. I learned modern vocal techniques, acting, dancing, methodology of teaching, history of music and music theory.

Skills

HTML5 • JavaScript • React.is • Web Development • Front-end Development • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Node.js • CSS Flexbox • English